280slides.com 2009-06-19

# 280 Slides - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At 280 North we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. (For example: we don’t save information about your activity on Slideshare when you publish presentations to their service.)
  * In 280 Slides, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, kept private, and permanently deleted.
  * We may from time to time e-mail you to let you know about new features in 280 Slides, but we'll always offer multiple ways to unsubscribe from all future e-mails.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

[](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) (This policy was inspired by [Automattic](http://automattic.com/), and is released under a **Creative Commons Sharealike** license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you.)

280 North, Inc. (“ **280 North** ”) operates several websites including [280Slides.com](http://280slides.com/) and [280North.com](http://280north.com/). It is 280 North's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, 280 North collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 280 North’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how 280 North’s visitors use its website. From time to time, 280 North may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

280 North also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 280 North does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to 280 North’s websites choose to interact with 280 North in ways that require 280 North to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that 280 North gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at [280Slides.com](http://280slides.com/) to provide an email address. In each case, 280 North collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with 280 North. 280 North does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

280 North may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, 280 North may monitor the most popular presentations on the [280Slides.com](http://280slides.com/). 280 North may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, 280 North does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

280 North discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 280 North’s behalf or to provide services available at 280 North’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using 280 North’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 280 North will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, 280 North discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when 280 North believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 280 North, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an 280 North website and have supplied your email address, 280 North may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with 280 North and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 280 North takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 280 North uses cookies to help 280 North identify and track visitors, their usage of 280 North website, and their website access preferences. 280 North visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 280 North’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of 280 North’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, 280 North may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in 280 North’s sole discretion. 280 North encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
